["It's In My Bloodline" playing]
[narrator] Previously on Love Island USA...
Six Islanders left the Villa.
[song continues]
[Sarah] Dumped from the island is...
Keenan.
[Kay Kay] I feel like I've found
what I came here for.
and I'd like to leave with Keenan.
[Sarah] The final safe girl is Johnnie.
I don't wanna continue this experience
if it's not with her.
The final safe boy is Zay.
♪ It's just my desire ♪
[narrator]
And a bombshell entered the villa.
Dude. what the heck?
-I was just watching you on my TV.
-I can imagine. Yeah.
-I like your eyes.
-I like yours as well.
♪ It's in my bloodline. yeah ♪
[narrator] Tonight...
[dramatic music playing]
...the new boy gets to work.
I'm not wearing underwear.
so I feel like I would...
-Oh. shit.
-Yeah. [laughs]
[narrator] Romance blossoms...
I am curious to explore that.
The feelings of attraction
have always been there.
[narrator] ...and heart rates soar.
[screams]
[theme song playing]
["Waiting All Night" playing]
♪ I've been waiting all night
Just to dance with you ♪
♪ You've been taking your time... ♪
[narrator] Welcome to Love Island USA.
Leonardo's created a shrine to Kassy
that looks romantic. thoughtful.
and most of all.
like someone's beloved cat's
just passed away.
But sadly for him. Kassy is off on a date
with new boy Scott.
-Kassy literally never came back.
-You're just making me stupid anxious.
We're just trying to figure out
where she is.
We don't know.
Damn.
-You can take me on that one.
-You down?
So it doesn't go to waste. you know?
[narrator] One minute nobody's interested.
The next. he's got two girls
fighting over him.
Yes. folks. Bergie has definitely been on
what we in the world of reality TV
describe as "a journey."
Okay. I did want to pull you.
I always hate this.
but I'm really feeling good
with Taylor right now.
And I just wanna keep pursuing that
with the time I have left in here.
-Yeah.
-And just see where things go.
-Okay. Thanks for pulling me.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-I just wanted to let you know. you know.
-Okay.
And you're still a great person.
I'm happy for you. you know.
You did. you know.
you've been exploring here.
so it's good that you found someone.
Yeah. And we're just connecting
on so many levels.
and I just wanna see it all the way out.
I'm happy for you. Oh. my God.
-Team Bergie and Taylor.
-Yeah.
-Good for you. though.
-Thank you.
I just really wanted to tell you
how I was feeling.
And I appreciate that so much
'cause that takes a lot of courage.
I'm very happy that you're.
you know. in a good place right now.
Bergie. he's happy
where he's at with Taylor.
You know. me and Kyle.
I just closed things there.
You know. I have been having
a hard time in here.
Any advice for me? Like...
-Just in life or in general.
-Just take everything at your own tempo.
There were some girls in here
that I was just trying to force it with
'cause I had no other option.
And then someone else shows up
and they show interest in you
-and you don't have to force anything.
-It's just natural.
-Oh. God.
-That would be my advice.
["DiGrace" playing]
Just make sure you take things
wherever you feel comfortable.
Don't... don't force it. Yeah.
♪ Is it blasphemy?
A catastrophe waiting? ♪
There's Kassy.
-Give me a hug.
-Thank you so much.
-[Imani] No hard feelings.
-[Bergie] Yeah.
♪ Stripping with intention ♪
Oh.
♪ Teaching you a lesson
I forgot to mention ♪
Hey. girl!
-Oh. you look so pretty!
-Thank you.
Wow! Gorgeous!
-Imani. can I talk to you?
-Of course!
Kassandra. where have you been?
[Kassy] I don't know!
We're going.
[Kassy] I'll pull you in a little bit.
Okay.
♪ I'm a criminal ♪
♪ It's subliminal though ♪
♪ So you lay down your cards
Or baby it's over ♪
♪ Head upon my shoulder... ♪
What's going on?
I don't know.
-Imani.
-Mm-hmm.
Somebody is out there.
and we have a sneaky link.
-Shh. Don't react too much.
-I see.
It's a secret.
I had a date with him. His name is Scott.
-Great guy.
-Yeah?
We both deserve this.
The gods are looking out for us.
so let's go.
[both squeal]
[Imani] My favorite girl
is taking me to meet a man!
Okay. I gotta pull it together.
-Okay. Let's go.
-Let's fucking do it. girl.
-Let's go. [clears throat]
-You look amazing.
[Kassy] You look amazing.
[Carmen] Where are you going?
I'm just taking her somewhere. Love you.
[Carmen] Why are you being
so shady with me. Kassandra?
Kassandra?
[Zay] Oh. she's just leaving.
[song continues]
I got a date!
This is fucked!
Bye. Love you.
Fuck. dude.
Fucking hell!
This shit does not feel good.
My mind is like. fully fucked right now.
[narrator]
Imani's heading for her date with Scott.
Scott left Love Island UK
completely single after six weeks.
which is like going on a TV cooking show
and not bothering to turn on the oven.
Imani!
Hello. Scott!
How are you? You okay?
-I'm good. How are you?
-You look nice.
Thank you.
-Kinda... I'm your height today.
-How are you?
-You're handsome!
-Nice meeting you.
You as well.
Oh. such a gentleman.
I am. I am.
-Thank you.
-Gotta bring it.
I love it.
So...
Really quick. Sorry.
You have some makeup on your face.
[both laugh]
-There you go. Nice.
-Thanks. though.
Talk to me. How are you...
How are you finding it in there?
I mean. it's been going good.
It's a journey.
I'm excited to be here with you.
-I wasn't...
-Same!
-Yeah. I wasn't expecting this!
-Were you not?
No.
I like what I'm seeing.
-I like what I'm seeing.
-Good.
Yeah.
Where are you from?
-Wales.
-Wales?
Little country next to England.
I'm from California.
Definitely a Cali girl.
What do you do?
I work in a care home
for adults with special needs.
-Nice!
-Yeah! So. wait. What about you?
So. I was a professional footballer
or a soccer player. as you would call it.
Okay. Okay.
And then. I went onto the most recent
Love Island UK series
-where I was there for six weeks.
-Deadass.
And then. I left the villa
three weeks ago.
Oh. Okay.
Well. are you single at the moment?
-So. what is the situation right now?
-[sighs]
I'm walking in there right now.
-Yeah.
-Where are you at?
Um. I'm very much open.
I'm definitely somebody
who puts it out there how I'm feeling.
I won't keep you out of the loop. um...
So when I say I'm open...
Oh. sweetie. Yeah.
-You're open.
-I'm open.
-Have you ever been to the UK?
-Never.
-Never?
Maybe that's your problem. you're worrying
about American men too much.
[laughs] Maybe. You know what?
'Cause. yeah.
They're not doing me justice right now.
-I don't think they are.
-You don't think so?
No. Of course not.
Why are you still sat here
saying you're open?
Someone should have snapped you up.
Smart man. See. I like you.
You're a thinker. I like that.
Do you like the British accent?
It's sexy. I'm not gonna lie.
Perfect!
In your relationships. are you looking
for something more energetic?
Calm? What's your vibe?
-I need someone who gives me a bit back.
-Okay.
Which. from what I've seen from you.
I don't think that's gonna be
an issue at all.
Oh. don't put me on the spot.
You are on the spot now.
Don't get shy now.
[narrator]
After her date. Kassy's strutting around
like the cat that's got the cream.
Ah. to be clear. not the cat
that's currently lying in state
in Leonardo's shrine.
Carmen. do you wanna go talk?
[Carmen] Yeah.
Come on. bubba.
Yeah. 'cause you disappeared for hours
and you missed our toast.
[Kassy] Mm-hmm.
I'm doing my lip gloss.
I get a fucking text. dude.
[both giggling]
Listen. bitch.
Season Ten. Love Island.
with the one that was. um...
Scott. the blue-eyed guy.
He's stunning.
-Him! Stunning!
-He's stunning!
-[British accent] Stunning!
[Kassy laughs] Sit. sit. sit.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. And so. I met the guy.
[British accent] Accent. Amazing.
[normal voice] He's from Wales.
You know?
And eye contact was strong. bitch.
He was like... He's like.
"The eye contact is good."
And I was like.
"Yeah. it's good. It's really good."
Can we just have a bro date on the beach
at this point?
Yeah.
You wanna go have the date. Leo?
I'll go have the date with you.
[Leonardo groans. laughs]
I haven't been this anxious in so long.
Oh. my God. bro.
I'm actually. like. freaking out.
[laughing] You...
Fuck you. Johnnie.
[no audible dialogue]
God. God. God. God.
-You needed this. baby!
-Fuck. yeah!
-Hey!
-Hi.
You guys busy?
No! We actually just wrapped up.
-Yeah.
-Love ya.
Love you.
Hello. suspect.
Hello.
Where were you?
Mmm?
On a date?
-Mmm. Uh-uh.
-No?
Can I ask you on a date?
Aw. you wanna ask me on a date?
-Yeah.
-Really?
-Is that okay?
-Mm-hmm.
Come on. You look amazing. by the way.
Thank you. Very vanilla.
[whispering] Oh. here we go.
...is. um... Oh. shit.
Well. you said do a grand gesture.
-[Kassy laughs]
-So. I...
-Stop right now.
-Yeah.
[Kassy] Aw.
[Leonardo]
Yeah. So. I made this big-ass heart.
[Kassy] Aw. that's so cute.
Thank you. Leo.
-[Leonardo] Are you okay?
-This is so cute.
-Yeah!
-Yeah.
Well...
[both laugh]
We don't need that part anyway.
Um...
I just wanted to. like...
just show you how I felt about you
instead of just tell you.
Like. I wasn't expecting to...
to fall this hard for somebody. you know?
And then. for me to have ruined that
was really one of the worst feelings ever.
This is so sweet and stuff.
-[gasps] Kenzo!
-[Kenzo] Hola. hola.
[speaking Spanish]
[speaking English] So we have...
"Tres Besos."
-Ooh. Tres Besos.
-[Leonardo] Gracias. señor.
Of course.
Wow.
It's so pretty.
-It's tilted.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
-Cheers!
[Leonardo]
Just the name of it. the three besos.
That was one of my favorite things
to do with you.
And it's just hard 'cause it's. like.
there's not a day that you walk by
in this house. even now.
that I... I don't see you walk by
and my heart doesn't sink to my ass.
You make me feel a type of way
I haven't felt in a very long time.
Like. in a very long time.
And I feel like I'd be an idiot
to not express that to you.
-I care about you still. um...
-Mm-hmm.
It's just...
It's different feelings now in a way.
Like. the romance.
I had to close that door.
I poured my heart out
just for it to be. like...
stabbed and then given back to me.
you know?
I don't wanna lie and be like.
"Oh. this is everything I need."
Like. "We can go back to the way it was"
because I...
I don't think so. and like...
I'd rather build. like.
a really strong friendship with us again.
how it was.
than... go back to romance.
not fully trusting you.
I've just fallen so hard for you. Kassy.
["See You In My Dreams" playing]
The only purpose I have in this villa
at this point
is to just try my hardest to show
you can trust me again.
And if you feel as if
you can't ever do that.
then I'd rather just go home.
♪ Now this road we travel ♪
♪ Will never be the same again ♪
♪ And I wanna believe
You're in a better place ♪
Definitely sad.
just to hear in that conversation
that she'd rather just be friends.
It just hurts because
I'm the reason why the walls went up.
What do I do at this point?
It just sucks.
It sucks real bad.
[song fades out]
["Watch Me" playing]
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
After six weeks on the UK show.
Scott's heading into
his second Love Island villa this summer.
He can't stay long
'cause a week on Tuesday
he's due on Love Island Mongolia.
♪ I got somethin' to show you ♪
♪ Yeah. you won't believe your eyes ♪
Hey!
-People. how are we?
-Hey. y'all!
[Kenzo] Oh. crap.
Oh. shit.
-New people?
-Let's go. Yeah.
-Scott.
-What's up?
-How are we. mate?
-Kenzo. Nice to meet you.
-Who is this?
-Kyle.
-This is my date!
-What's up. baby?
-You good. bro?
-Yeah.
Bergie! I've heard all about you.
-Scott. How are you?
-Good.
Everyone. do you all wanna
go around the fire pit?
Just get everyone round.
Let's go.
♪ Watch me. just watch me now ♪
-He's British. He's from...
-He's from the UK one.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-He was with Catherine. remember?
I definitely think a lot of girls
are gonna have their head on a swivel
now that he's in.
He's got that... he's got that accent
going for him too. you know?
[Scott] Oh. fuck. I've not met you.
Scott. Nice to meet you.
How are you. mate? You okay?
Scott from Love Island UK.
Which is really weird
'cause we were just watching
his Love Island
before we came into our Love Island.
And now. he's at our Love Island.
-So. who's seen the UK one?
-I watched it.
-Yeah.
You know. Right. yeah. So. yeah.
I spent six weeks in the UK one.
Three weeks ago I was in there.
Got to the final week.
The girl I was with. I friend-zoned her
in the final week. so I come out single.
-Welcome.
-Well. welcome. Yeah.
Yeah. good. Nice to meet you all. anyway.
So out of the girls. who's closed off.
who's not?
Let's put it out there.
-I'm closed off.
-[Scott] So you two are closed off.
-So. I was expecting that.
-I feel like I'm closed off as well.
-Closed off?
-[Taylor S] Yeah.
-[Scott] To the big man?
-[all] Bergie!
You got it. Let's go!
When Taylor raised her hand I was just...
I just felt a sense of relief.
Like. we're feeling really strong
about our connection.
And now. she's showing everybody
how strong our connection is.
So. obviously.
I had the date with Kassy and Imani.
That's fucking wild!
I didn't even know this.
Youse don't know about this?
So they snuck out.
I had a date with both of them.
How have yous left this one single?
-And this one. Both of them. I can't...
-He's a smart man.
-Which date did you like more?
-They were both good dates. you know?
-Come on. Come on. mate.
-Ah. Safe answer.
You're not gonna get that out of me.
-[Kyle] We're already in the game.
-Big dick energy. I love it.
I love it.
[electronic music playing]
-Imani. I love this for you. girl.
-I know.
-Holy shit.
-He's nice.
He is fine as fuck!
-Johnnie!
-He is cute!
Girl. he fine. He's fine. Little...
He's a fine little.
you know. UK delectable.
Yeah. You know what?
European people...
European people. they're very sexual.
-They like that banter. Yeah!
-And they're very blunt.
I think some of the boys
should be worried.
They should be standing on their toes
a little bit because he has the charm.
he has the sex appeal
and he has the confidence.
And I don't know what it is.
but something about the UK boys.
they know how to get a woman.
Y'all. he got
a little flavor to him. though.
-I mean. you know. he got good taste.
-Oh. my God!
-He got good taste.
-I love that.
Thank you. Love Island gods!
Yes. send me a man.
They sent me a man! Like...
He's a fine little man. He's handsome.
I think he can handle my energy.
which I do like.
And just. you know. me as a person.
So that was very attractive. you know?
We could have fun together.
-Hello.
-Join us.
That also just shows
he loves a bad bitch woman.
-He loves a woman with that energy.
-A boss ass energy.
-He tells it how it is.
-Yeah.
I like that. That's nice.
We need someone like that
who appreciates that.
-And doesn't repress it.
-[Imani] Oh. my God.
-They're not intimidated by it.
-And that... Okay. I liked the energy.
-Was it natural for you at first?
-Yes. So natural. dude!
Sitting there. like.
we just started giggling
'cause I'm like. "Oh. shit. I know you."
And he was giggling too.
And the eye contact was really strong.
Girl. he was freaking
staring into my soul.
I'm like. "What the fuck?"
It's like the Love Island gods
were looking out for us.
Wait. So. you went on your date with him
and then came back?
Yeah. I come back
and Leo comes and grabs me.
He just expressed how. like.
I'm the only person here for him.
He expressed how he is...
I think he said he's in love with me
or he's falling.
Whatever.
He kept going back and forth with it.
I said. "But if I'm being honest.
romantically. I closed the door."
I was like. friendship-wise. though...
I was not... Sorry. I wasn't expecting you
to say that. sweetheart. What?
That's what you told him?
-Yeah.
-[Imani] Wow!
[Kassy]
You know. I still care about him so much.
[Taylor S] Kassy. that's crazy.
I'm so fucking proud of you. baby.
-I mean...
-Good for you. girl!
I'm proud of me. too.
Girl. you stood your ground.
Tap on my back.
-Kassy. this is huge.
-This is huge.
'Cause I thought
you was gonna fold like a folding chair.
I care about Leo so much. and I still
wanna be friends with the guy.
And as much as I would love for it
to be how it was. it...
it just isn't.
It's hard to forgive
what's already been done.
And. you know.
if I'm really somebody's person.
then they'll do anything to not lose me.
You've now learned...
-You know your self-worth.
-Yeah.
And you know that you deserve someone
who is gonna treat you like that.
but never disrespect you the way he did.
So. you know. how did your date go?
I'm just kinda confused
on where we leave off
because she was like.
"I still have these feelings for you.
But I kinda paused the romance part
because I don't know
if I could trust you again."
And I don't blame her.
Like. I'm tired. bro. I'm at my wit's end.
That's the only girl I care about.
And it fucking sucks
because I threw it all away for no reason.
One night.
[Leonardo] And it's terrible. bro.
Yeah. Dude. I completely understand.
And watching you put your heart
on the line like that.
and doing what you truly feel.
what your heart tells you to do.
it just shows. you know.
how true you are to what you believe.
and how true you are
to how you feel about her.
She's never gonna forget that.
[Marco]
Yeah. she's never gonna forget that.
I'm so drained out.
Like. I wanted to cry during that date
because it's like.
I'm looking at this girl
that I could see the entire world with...
and it just hurts knowing that. like.
I'm the reason why it wasn't continued.
And we were both falling for each other
at the same rate.
And it's just like.
I've never felt so crushed
to see the girl that I have
such strong feelings for every day.
and can't fully express that.
Dude. that hurts me.
That's so tough.
[narrator] Goalie Scott's
not hanging around in there.
If he'd shown this kind of
impressive speed and decision making
with his soccer team.
he might still be playing for them.
Johnnie? Wanna go for a chat?
Uh. yes. Sorry.
Sorry. I'll be back. guys.
-[Johnnie] Hi.
-[Scott] How are you? You okay?
-Yeah. Nice to meet you.
-Where do you wanna go?
[Johnnie] Let's go to Breathe.
Right. Talk to me
about your situation now.
I was in a situation with. um. Leo.
I needed to make sure that book was closed
before I reopened it with everyone else.
-Yeah. How old are you. by the way?
-I'm 26.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-Do you know how old I am?
-No.
-Twenty-two.
-Oh.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Do you feel like
you're more emotionally mature and...
I mean. I'd say I'm more mature. yeah.
I've lived away from home
from the age of about 14.
so I had no choice.
I grew up and moved out of my mom's house
when I was 17.
and I grew up very. very fast. so...
I come from a very. um. artsy family.
So my sister is a tattoo artist.
My mom's a graffiti artist.
-Do you have any tattoos?
-I do.
-Where?
-I have four.
There's one.
-So. this is one.
-Yeah.
I can't see any.
so I feel like the other ones
-are gonna be in much better places.
-[laughing]
Where are the others?
Um...
-I'm missing three.
-Yeah.
-One right here.
-Ah. that's the one place I was missing.
-Okay. So. that's three.
-I was 16.
No excuse.
I have one on my ass.
-Like. on it?
-Yeah.
Oh. Jesus Christ.
Oh. my God.
It just gets worse.
[laughing] It just gets...
-You're gonna see it at some point anyway.
-Am I now?
I'm not wearing underwear.
so I feel like...
-Oh. shit.
-Yeah. I can't...
Shit! Fucking hell.
He is... Scott is very...
Scott is very. very good-looking.
This is the first time
since I've been here
that I've felt nervous.
Every time I've had feelings for somebody.
I'm good at keeping my co... composure.
I don't know.
Just. the giddiness level
is definitely not comparable
to when I met Leo.
People with colored eyes are always...
They always have to just...
Mm-hmm.
-It's too much.
-This is how we put people on the spot.
This is how we make you speechless
like you were then.
-I'm not speechless.
-You've been speechless twice.
-Ah...
-Oh. there you go.
Done. Gone. There we go.
[narrator] So. Taylor S and Bergie
are both proudly closed off.
Big deal.
I've been emotionally closed off
my entire life.
and you don't see me
going around boasting about it.
-Back up here.
Take the earrings out. I'm just kidding.
Yeah. I know. I'm like. "Fuck 'em!"
-Johnnie's like. "Those are my earrings!"
-Johnnie's like. "Hey. hey. hey!"
Oh. my gosh. How crazy.
-I know. What a crazy night.
-Yeah.
I...
-Well. you know where my head's at.
-Yeah. definitely.
Even if another girl walked in
at this point.
like. I just wanna ride us out
and see how far our connection can go.
-Yeah.
-I'm totally closed off.
I just feel like there's no one
who I've had. like.
a connection like this with
in terms of just making me feel like...
just wanted. and like. always...
like. you are such a good listener. too.
And the fact that. like.
you just make me feel so secure...
[Bergie] Mm-hmm.
It's something that I've never had. like...
You know. being in. like.
something with someone.
So... I know I just...
I don't think my head would really turn.
Being exclusive with Taylor feels like
the right thing to do in this moment.
Definitely liking the pace
that we're going at.
It finally feels like
I'm in a comfortable spot.
It took a while. It was worth the fight.
And now I can just relax. explore it.
I'm just comfortable all the time.
I'm in the same boat.
Yeah. We're good.
[narrator] It's been one hell of a night.
Sadly. Destiny missed it
'cause she wasn't feeling well.
But new boy Scott's
brought experience. wisdom.
and most importantly.
his personalized suitcase and water bottle
from the UK show.
So he saved us
having to get the stickers out.
["Line of Sight" playing]
♪ In my way ♪
♪ I won't go there till it's over
I'll fight another day ♪
[Kassy] Guys. what a crazy night.
-[Hannah W] Hey. hey.
-[Kassy] Holy shit.
♪ Isolation. separation ♪
♪ It always ends in hate
And it never stops ♪
♪ But I will keep my line of sight ♪
♪ My line of sight ♪
He's very. very. very confident.
He's gonna mix shit up in here.
If there's two people who deserve love
like the most in life in here.
it's Kassy and I.
Be careful. but...
I will stick beside my man. though.
Good luck out there.
Good luck out there. [laughs]
And I'm off to bed.
[Marco] Look how fat they are.
Holy shit!
-[Hannah] I feel bad. They're so big.
-Why are they so fat?
It was... it was so natural.
And. you know. it was fun.
It was. you know. playful. but I liked it.
[Hannah] Seem like a cool. chill dude.
-We shall see. girl.
We shall see.
♪ My line of sight ♪
[Kassy]
I did pretty much close the door with Leo.
I'm so. so proud of you.
Yeah. I'm proud of myself.
It's very inspiring to see
that you weren't swayed that way.
No grand gesture will ever make up
for somebody disrespecting you.
Like. we've grown love as friends.
but. like. the love you have for yourself
is another love
that you got to get in here.
No matter what. you're leaving with love.
Exactly.
♪ My line of sight ♪
[song ends]
["I'm All Fired Up" playing]
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Scott's only just arrived.
but when those lights went out.
that boy was up all night long.
Not in a sexy way.
He's just got very bad jet lag.
♪ Something caught my eye
Made my mouth run dry ♪
♪ Felt the slowing hands of time... ♪
-Welcome. Scott.
-How are you doing. Scott?
I'm good. [chuckles]
These beds are nice.
[both chuckle]
Well. I thought it's gonna be
a great day in the villa.
Good morning. guys!
Wake the hell up!
Good morning! Good morning!
-Good morning!
-Oh. God.
-You're so excited in the morning. Jesus.
-I am.
[song continues]
Ow. That fucking hurt.
-Good morning.
What's up?
Okay. I'll get out.
This is all in pounds. innit?
-Yeah. You're confused?
-I don't know what the fuck's going on.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
♪ Now the lines been drawn ♪
♪ And to keep this story short ♪
♪ Let's just say I want a little more ♪
-I've never even met someone from Wales.
-Have you ever met any British people?
Maybe. like. real briefly.
but I never...
I don't have a British friend or nothing.
Do you guys have. like. bro code. kinda?
-Yeah.
-You act like they're from like. Mars.
-Well. I don't know.
-[Carmen] No. literally.
[song continues]
[song ends]
Hey. guys.
-How are you doing today?
-I'm feeling exclusive.
-Oh. yeah?
-[Bergie] Pretty good.
-Exclusive. That's a word.
-Bergie!
Oh. I'm super excited
just to keep pursuing Taylor
and to see where things go.
-[Kenzo] All yours now.
-[Bergie] Yeah. it's gonna be fun.
Yeah. And she said that yesterday.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
We're just gonna ride this thing out
and see what we can do after the villa.
Hell. yeah.
[Taylor S] Ooh. yes.
-Yes.
-Hi. baby.
-Des. yay!
-[Taylor S] Destiny!
-[Carmen] Are you okay?
-I'm so happy you're okay.
[Kassy] Do you feel good?
-Yeah.
-Have you heard the news?
No. I actually have to get this.
So. what's going on. y'all?
[Carmen] We have a new friend.
He's from Love Island UK.
-This season.
-[Taylor S] And he's now in the Villa.
-And he's here?
-Yeah.
-[Destiny] What?
He's from Wales. He's 22.
Brown hair. blue eyes.
Bullet blue.
Okay. Y'all know my type is easy.
I know. That's why I was. like.
"Someone bring her in.
-Where's she at?"
-"Go get her."
Wait. he's in the kitchen.
Do you wanna peek out?
Let's go. Let's go. peek.
Peek. peek. Let's go. Let's go.
[Kassy] Just do a peekaboo.
Uh. can you see him?
[laughing]
Zay.
First rule of thumb.
Need to talk to Destiny.
I don't know where she is.
Definitely that's priority number one.
Need to have a conversation with her.
express to her my openness.
[Kenzo] Are you ending things
with Destiny.
or are you just letting her know
that you're gonna be open?
That'll probably be a tough conversation.
to be honest.
Yeah. it's gonna be a tough conversation.
but it's just... I'm just gonna have
to lay it out exactly how I feel
and not really worry about
how she's gonna take it.
I just kinda have to just let her know
and she can take it however she chooses.
I think that's a great idea.
especially dealing with Destiny.
It's been my primary objective
to talk to Destiny
and clarify things with Destiny.
I tried to be open and honest with her
in terms of me seeing if other
connections were there with other people.
I deserve the ability
to find the strongest connection.
just as everybody else in here.
Actually. I got some venting to do.
-[Kassy] Yes. Go ahead.
-[Carmen] Yeah.
Okay. So. he told me leaving Casa.
that he was okay
with me tying up things with Mike.
And then when we got back.
he just completely switched.
Switched. like. it was like a new person.
So. it's cool. though.
Everything happens for a reason.
I'm glad it came out sooner
rather than later.
-[Carmen] Yeah.
-Yeah.
[narrator] After last night's date.
Leonardo's not giving in with Kassy.
It's like the old saying.
"If at first you succeed.
then sleep with someone else during Casa
and ruin everything.
try. try again."
-Hello. fuckers.
-Hi. fucker.
Can I pull you for a conversation?
-[chuckles] Not a chat.
-Conversation.
"Can I pull you for a conversation?"
-Let me put my heels on.
-Terrible.
Oh. shit.
-What's up?
-What's up. brother?
Hey. my brothers.
I know you're gonna fucking despise me.
but I need to use this booth.
if that's okay.
Take her to Soul Ties.
-Hell. no. Get outta here.
-Fuck that.
-The curse started with us.
-Ain't nothing good comes from Soul Ties.
-Didn't mean to ruin the math. I know.
-Do what you gotta do. brother.
-All good.
-Yeah.
-[Kassy giggles]
-[Kyle sighs]
[Kassy] Shit.
-Hello. Kassandra.
-Hello. [grunts]
-[Leonardo] How are you feeling. though?
-Good. like...
I'm feeling...
good. [laughs]
-You're terrible.
-I'm proud of myself.
I'm not telling you nothing.
-Oh. is that so?
-Mm-hmm.
I know you owe it to yourself
to explore your connections here
and do the things that you wanna do. but...
End of the day. I would be lying
to myself if I said I didn't miss you
and that I'm not still in love with you.
'cause. you know...
You're not. Get out of here.
Oh my... I'm so fucking corny.
I made a poem about it.
-Get the fuck out of here.
-It's mad corny.
I was like.
"Bro. I'm not... I'm not saying this shit.
She's just gonna laugh at me."
Well. you said it. You brought it up.
so you have to read it now.
Okay.
"Roses are red. violets are blue.
I sincerely miss being beside of you.
The days are long. the nights are longer.
Yet somehow my feelings for you
keep growing stronger.
Although I've messed up.
it's clear to see.
that you're the only girl
who was meant for me.
Kassy Castillo. you've stolen my heart.
and there's no way I'd leave here
without pouring out my entire heart."
Aw. that's really nice.
But like. I don't remember the last time
I felt like a little kid.
Like. really falling for somebody.
I can honestly say I've never had a poem
written about me.
It was really nice.
The fact that he's also
still letting me know how he feels.
It's like. surprising.
because I... I thought
he would have given up by now.
I closed the door.
He's still trying to get in.
so [sighs] it's a hard one.
You know. I want you to do
whatever it is that you wanna do.
It can be literally anything.
I feel like you aren't taking no
for an answer. and like...
I'm not gonna take no for an answer
until you literally say...
exactly the words.
"Pull all the way back."
But you haven't.
Why is that?
[sighs] Well. this was fun. Let's go.
-[laughs] Let's go.
-Jesus Christ.
Yeah. well. that was a nice chat.
-All right. You do your thing.
-It was a good chat.
-Nice chat. Adios.
-You motherfucker. yo.
-Bye.
-Bye. [laughs]
She hasn't told me
to not stop applying pressure.
and she seems to enjoy
that I'm applying pressure.
So. seeing that it's giving
a green light type of scenario.
I'm gonna keep doing that
because that's the only girl I care about.
[sighs]
Fuck.
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Air Force man Zay is over Destiny
and ready for the singles scene.
I offered to be his wingman.
but apparently that requires
US citizenship.
five years training
and a valid pilot's license.
I just. like... I don't know.
I have no intention
of beating around the bush
or like. anything like that.
or trying to. like.
waste either of our time.
-Like. I just wanna have a conversation.
-Well...
Yeah. I'm not ready to talk to you.
You're not ready to talk to me?
-No.
-Why is that?
Because I'm not.
I don't really have an answer for that.
-Um... [stammers]
-No.
I don't want... I don't expect any answers.
I don't really have any...
I'm not expecting any answers.
Well. I'm gonna walk away now
'cause I told you no.
-I just wanna let you know that...
-I don't.
-I'm gonna be open with other people.
-No.
I don't wanna talk to you. Zay.
Do you not understand that?
-I don't understand how that's fair...
-Easy.
Like. how you could just not hear me out
and just walk away?
This has been
an ongoing communicative issue
since we came into the villa.
This is my experience
and I deserve the ability
to find the strongest connection
just as everybody else in here.
That's exactly what I knew
was gonna happen.
[narrator] Hey. Kassy. my wee flower.
when you hear me talking about you.
what's the first thing
that comes into your tiny little head?
Nice accent.
It is.
I like Irish. though.
Irish is always my number one.
If they would have brought
an Irishman on here...
-Done. done.
-[Kassy] Mmm.
I would have gone home with him
the first day.
Irish is always my number one.
They brought a girl
that looked just like me. so...
[laughs]
-First of all. you should be grateful.
-Yeah.
-First of all. you should be lucky.
We kind of match. too.
I know.
The vibe is vibing.
I'm thirsty. I want my bottle. actually.
Need to switch up my heels. too.
Ooh.
Little wet.
[both laugh]
[Kassy] Is it sweat?
[Johnnie] No. it's not sweat.
-My toe is bleeding.
-Why are you so suspicious?
-I'm not suspicious.
-You are suspicious.
[Carmen] I don't want any part of this.
-Oh. my God. Both of you.
-What is she doing?
Why are you giggling like that?
[Kassy] Because we're turned on.
I had to walk away.
I was. you know. into Kassy's looks
when I first saw her
because she's very beautiful.
very much my type.
So the feelings of attraction
have always been there.
I am bisexual. and I just didn't wanna
make anyone uncomfortable.
Like. open that door and especially
if I wasn't reading it right
or gauging it right.
If she really wanted to pursue that.
she should come to me.
So what were you guys
being suss about over here?
Can you fill me in now?
I literally was just getting turned on
by Johnnie. That was it.
[singsongy] Child.
Dude. avocados is ready.
[Destiny] They're ready? How do you know?
-Depending on how soft they are.
-Destiny.
-Oh. yeah?
-Let's go.
Let's do it. Let's do it.
-What are you making?
-Guac.
I'll get some water and then...
Guacamole. Do you like guac?
-Guacamole?
-Oh. shit. Yeah.
No. I'm not really a massive fan.
-I'm not gonna lie.
-What?
-Yeah.
-Let's do it. I'll follow you.
He's been getting to know a lot of people.
Um. I think he's doing his thing.
Who do you think he's feeling?
[Destiny] So. welcome.
Nice surprise. but hey. welcome.
-Was it a nice surprise?
-It was a nice surprise.
-Thank you. Like an American accent.
-I have a thick accent.
We call this Southern.
In the UK. I'm northern.
-so this is a northern.
-Oh. it's a northern.
Yeah. It's not the. uh.
the quintessential British.
Okay. What's the difference?
-Give me... give me an example.
-I don't know.
Yeah. The London one is like...
[sharp accent] All right. geez?
You're doin' my head in.
Fackin' 'ell.
[normal accent]
Mine's a little bit different.
[laughing] A little bit different.
A little bit different to that.
It's different. for sure.
Yeah. Talk to me.
Tell me about you and where you're at now.
Well. I'm Destiny. clearly.
-Yeah. I know that.
-You know that much.
Uh. I'm from St. Louis. Missouri.
so the US.
-What do you do?
-I'm a microbiologist.
Okay. Jesus.
-Pretty fancy.
-Wow.
Pretty intelligent. Yeah.
-That's caught me off guard.
-Yeah.
-Thank you.
-Well. fair enough.
Yeah. inside the villa.
I'm technically in a couple with Zay.
-[Scott] Yeah.
-And I did bring him back from Casa Amor.
So. where have you left it? So...
-Oh. we're done.
-Done. Over.
Over.
Like. that door is definitely shut.
You tell me about yourself.
What do you look for in a woman?
What do I look for? So obviously.
I need a girl who gives me a bit back.
I can't walk all over someone. Um...
I feel like I'm a strong personality.
Quite confident and that.
-I need to have banter with them as well.
-Okay.
I feel like you're a character. though.
I don't feel like
that's gonna be an issue for you.
-I'm definitely a character.
-You're a character.
Oh. my... Naturally.
Just not even trying to be.
It just happens.
I feel like the girls in here
are very straightforward with things.
-Yeah. for sure.
-I like that.
because that's exactly how I am.
-Really?
-Yeah. I need someone to be like that.
-That's good.
-We do our thing over here.
You do do your thing.
-We don't sugarcoat very much at all.
-Good stuff.
You feel like you've had the experience.
You feel like you've had it all. innit?
There's one little inch missing.
We're gonna see if we can complete that
from here on out.
You better do your thing. Scott. [laughs]
[narrator] Kassy's realized
that she's attracted to Johnnie.
and that's what we
in the world of reality TV
describe as "shaking up the format."
[Kassy] Oh. gosh.
Oh. my God.
[Johnnie] This is my first official
somebody pulling me for a chat up here.
-Really? Yay.
-Yeah. It's very romantic.
-I feel so nervous now.
-[Kassy] Me too. I'm nervy.
[Johnnie] Oh. my gosh.
I can't believe you pulled me.
I know. I was waiting for you to pull me.
-We haven't had time.
-Yeah. So I was like. okay.
fuck it. I'm gonna pull you and see.
Why can't I just pull you too.
-So. you look good.
-You look good.
[Kassy squeals. laughs]
Yeah. No. I'm glad you did pull me
'cause I was like. you know. I'm bisexual.
but I'm not sexually attracted
to just everyone.
Yeah.
-And also I have to feel it back.
-Yeah.
But that's why I feel like
it goes so well with you.
Because we. like... I feel it.
And I can tell
when somebody else actually feels it.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I just get nervy.
I get nervy
because. like. I've never dated a girl.
so I... I am curious to like. explore that.
I just didn't know. like...
I guess I was just trying to figure out
what I was feeling and stuff.
and see if like. it could be something.
I don't know.
-It's there.
-Yeah.
It's there.
But we just haven't...
It's like the line.
-It's like not being...
-Yeah.
We're like... Keep dipping our toes in it.
I know.
I just wanted to...
["One Spark" playing]
♪ It only takes one spark
To light up everything... ♪
I obviously find you attractive.
[giggling] Obviously.
Um. I just didn't know if you felt. like.
the attraction too. and stuff.
so I just wanted to. like. see
if you're seeing that. I don't know.
Bitch. I've been seeing it.
What do you mean?
Okay. okay. I just wanted to know.
like. we joke around and stuff.
but. like. I didn't know
if it was really joking or not.
I'm not joking.
[laughing] Me neither.
Me neither.
♪ Oh. nothing's gonna be the same ♪
Boys. But also just.
I kept looking at you.
I kept wanting to talk to you.
And so I was like. I'm low-key down.
-Not low-key. I am down.
-Yeah.
I like people
that bring out a fun side in me.
And I feel fun when I'm with you.
I feel comfortable when I'm with you.
I feel like... You know what I mean?
Those aren't things that you find
in people very often. where you're like...
you get to be somebody else
when you're with them.
Yeah. And just like. when I'm seeing you.
I'm like...
I would think like.
"We'd be cute in a way.
Like. "We'd be cute together."
Um. and then. like. also.
I wouldn't mind exploring more. um.
just whenever. so...
[song continues]
So. how about now?
♪ Feeling something ♪
♪ Like I've never known ♪
♪ A fire ♪
♪ I don't know how to explain ♪
♪ Feeling like it's all or nothing ♪
♪ I can't let it go ♪
That felt good.
[both laugh]
I knew it.
It got too quiet.
-[Kassy] Stop.
-[Johnnie] It got too quiet.
[both laughing]
[Kassy] Oh. my God.
Oh. my God. it got too quiet.
[Johnnie] It got too quiet.
I liked kissing her.
I really liked kissing her.
It just felt right.
My friends definitely told me.
they were like. "You're bi."
I'm like.
"Well. I haven't had anything with a girl.
so I'm not sure yet."
My mom. I haven't really talked
about it with her.
But at the same time.
I know that she wouldn't care
'cause. like. she just wants me
to be happy.
So if she sees me happy. she'll be happy.
I know that.
-Anyways.
-So. I'm excited.
-Me. too.
-Soul Ties is crazy.
[Kassy] Carmen?
-Yeah. bubba?
-Let's go talk.
-Okay.
-Good chat?
-Good chat.
-Nice.
-Where should we go?
-Um. either or.
Um. let's go to Breathe.
So it's more far away.
Um. so I just wanted to. like...
Obviously. me and...
Well. I don't know if you know.
but me and Johnnie. just like.
we jokingly. like. flirt.
-Yeah.
-But. like. it was just like...
Then it got where
it didn't feel like a joke.
-Wait. are you being serious?
-Yeah.
I thought you knew I was curious.
but I'm like. maybe not.
No. I... you guys just flirt so much.
But y'all are always funny about it.
Yeah. So we just went up there
and we were talking about it.
Um...
[laughing] And then we kissed.
[Carmen] Like...
You guys had a good talk?
It was good? Good chat?
Kassy did open up to me. just being like.
"I'm actually very. like. interested."
-So it did open the door for us.
-Yeah.
Like. my door has been open.
but I never thought that she was serious.
-Because...
-No. Yeah. she's serious.
-How was the kiss?
-It was good.
-Did you feel something?
-I did. Yeah.
Oh. this is crazy.
It's crazy.
For the short-lived moment that it was.
it was actually a very. very good kiss.
Um. and I think that we both...
Like. the sexual tension
has been rising and rising and rising.
So I think that we both needed to see.
The feelings of attraction
have always been there.
but nobody was making the first move.
And I felt like it was more so for her
to come pull me
because if I pulled her
and it was just kind of like.
"Oh. I wasn't feeling that."
I would have been extremely embarrassed.
So I think I was just waiting for her
to kind of make the initial step.
[Kassy] So that was nice. [chuckles]
But it's also like.
just us opening the door to it.
Are both of you... Like. are you both bi?
-Are you just bi-curious?
-[Kassy] She's bi.
I told her I was curious.
I also. like. kept looking at her.
I would catch myself checking her out.
And so I was like... So I just didn't know
if it was. like. jokes
or if it was like...
If it really was something.
But I do find her attractive.
But I'm stuck also with Leo.
He read me a fucking poem.
Romantically. I can't open that door.
I'm like. shocked
that he's even pulling me
and reads me that poem.
Great poem.
I've never had anybody write me a poem.
And the fact that. like.
he sees me talking to Scott.
he sees me talking to Johnnie.
and he still is showing me. like.
"It's still you."
And after that he tells me
he's in love with me.
What about Scott. though?
How are you feeling about Scott?
[Kassy] Scott? It's a clean slate.
He hasn't done me dirty.
but at the same time. it's like.
I'm also really comfortable with Leo
because he was like my best friend.
But I'm just holding back from that
'cause I'm like.
do I wanna take that leap again
and hope that it doesn't pie me
in the face?
So right now. I'm choosing myself.
I'm figuring out what I want.
and it's confusing as it is.
But that's love. Love is confusing.
Love is a roller coaster.
Love is love.
So. yeah. that's all I can do.
So are you gonna tell Leo
that the door is kind of opening?
In a way. I don't wanna tell him.
Keeps him on his toes.
but at the same time...
[Carmen]
I want him to keep working for it.
I don't know if I would say
dive back into opening that door.
-Love you.
-I love you.
["On The Dance Floor" playing]
♪ Oh. I been waitin'
For the night so long ♪
♪ I need a moment ♪
♪ I need the rhythm of a good vibe song ♪
-I don't believe in wearing underwear.
-I don't either.
I like my vagina to see things
it doesn't get to see usually.
-Okay. Yeah.
-Yeah.
I got all the back pieces. [laughs]
[Marco] I like this shirt.
Put your fucking ass up.
you fucking... [laughs]
I dress every night
like as if a bombshell's coming in. dawg.
Yo. are those pajama pants?
♪ Take me up ♪
♪ All my cares on the dance floor ♪
♪ All my worries on the dance floor ♪
♪ All the long days on the dance floor ♪
[phone chimes]
-I got a text!
-[cheering]
-[phone chimes]
-[gasps]
-[Kassy] Oh. shit.
-[Carmen] Johnnie.
I got a text.
All right. all right. all right.
[reading]
[reading hashtags]
-We're doing the Hearts...
-[excited screaming]
It's a striptease. baby.
Oh. this is so embarrassing.
We're about to grind.
We're gonna have to grind
and throw it back.
Throw it back! Throw it back!
[Imani] And lift.
Yeah. do that one. do that one.
♪ On the dance floor ♪
[Taylor S] Girl!
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Tonight sees the return of Hearts On Fire.
First. the girls perform sexy dances
while the boys wear heart rate monitors.
Then the boys perform sexy dances
while the girls wear expressions
that say. "What on earth is he up to?"
So who will set pulses racing the most?
We'll see what this heart rate
gonna feel like.
-My heart's already racing.
-Mine too.
Me. too. Yeah. We're not even going yet.
Marco. don't fart.
Really?
-Who's your guess? Who's coming first?
-Uh...
Imani.
-I'm gonna guess...
Hannah or Carmen.
-Hannah or Carmen.
-Oh. yeah. I'd be nervous.
Oi!
["Good Life" playing]
♪ Come on ♪
[Leonardo] Oh. shit.
♪ I'm feeling so good
I can't even take it ♪
-Oh. shit.
-[Leonardo] Whoa.
-Geez.
-[whoops. laughs]
Hey. boys. This ain't my first rodeo.
I'm here to take you for a ride.
[cheering]
♪ Where the party don't stop
And we go all night ♪
I kind of blacked out
when I got out there.
and I was just like.
"Let me just do whatever feels right."
Good work.
I was blown away.
I was locked on her the whole time.
I was cheering her on.
My heart was beating.
[Kyle] I was like. "Holy shit."
Like. that girl can move.
Oh. boy.
Oh. shit.
I gotta. you know. do something for Marco.
you know.
a little more extra.
Oh. God.
Hey. hey!
Attaboy. Marco!
Yeah. there it is.
[Hannah] That was a workout.
Shout out to the strippers out there.
because damn. you need to be in shape.
[Leonardo] Way to go. baby!
Oh. my God. My heart's fucking racing.
Sturdy. Sturdy.
Did you see the tongue?
The tongue was crazy.
That was definitely fun.
-[Hannah] What?
-Hi. Hannah.
I get to watch now.
-[Kenzo] Let's go.
-[Leonardo] Hey.
["Bad Girl" playing]
[Hannah whoops] Let's go. Carmen.
Oh. my God.
Looks like she does this or something.
[Carmen] When I was walking out there.
I felt like the baddest bitch
in the world.
Before you ask.
it did hurt when I fell from heaven.
but I'm not feeling so angelic tonight.
♪ Sometimes you gotta be a bad girl ♪
♪ Sometimes you gotta be a bad. bad girl ♪
♪ It feels so good be a bad girl ♪
♪ It feels so good be a bad. bad girl ♪
[Marco] Yeah. Carmen.
Um... You know. honestly.
I am a little bit upset.
-I heard bad boys take you to heaven.
-To heaven? Nah. we go to hell.
Yeah. Carmen!
She's my girlfriend.
She got on him and gave him neck kisses.
To me. you know. that's just...
it's crossing the line.
[Zay] Whoo-hoo!
♪ It feels so good be a bad. bad girl ♪
I'm wifed up. but I felt like I gave them
a good enough taste
and a good enough look that maybe...
I can get their heart rates up
a little bit.
♪ Sometimes you gotta be a bad girl ♪
♪ Sometimes you gotta be a bad. bad girl ♪
My head's racing a little bit right now.
I don't know.
I don't know if she tried
to push my buttons or something.
[Marco] Good job. Carmen.
Good job. Carmen. Good job. Carmen.
[Bergie] Attagirl. Carmen!
Kinda hurt a little bit.
[speaking Spanish]
What do you think?
I was fine. A little too much.
[dramatic music plays]
We're all done now.
Yay! Got it over with.
-Hello. baby.
-Good job. babe.
I wish I got to see yours.
You did that. girl.
It's just a challenge.
-It's his girlfriend.
-I know.
It's my girlfriend.
And plus. like. I. like...
I wasn't even planning on. like.
dancing with the other girls.
-[Zay] Yeah.
-Like. I just wanted her.
["It Hurts" playing]
♪ I know that it hurts... ♪
[Carmen] Yeah. I don't think
he's very happy. though.
-Why?
-I don't know.
I think he's mad
that I went up to the other boys.
But I was like... 'Cause we set boundaries.
We're not gonna kiss anyone else
in challenges anymore.
-and I didn't.
-You didn't do that. You're good. girl.
The whole point of the game
is to raise heart rates.
Yeah.
[Carmen] He was just dead silent.
Leo and Marco had to start cheering for me
'cause he wouldn't.
♪ I know that it hurts ♪
Oh. he's so mad at me. Fuck.
[Carmen]
I don't feel fucking cute anymore.
I don't feel sexy. I feel like ass.
I wanna go in the bathroom and cry.
-And you made me feel that way.
-Stop.
[Carmen] I would never date a guy
who would make me feel the same way.
'cause I have and I won't do it again.
[theme song playing]